Only one way out.
400 Bullets is a action, war, mystery film directed by Tom Paton.
One cold winter night in Afghanistan is about to get a whole lot worse for Rana Rae, a Gurkha soldier left to guard a British military
outpost, when Captain Noah Brandt arrives looking for refuge from a group of rogue special ops and a cell of heavily armed Taliban.
The two soldiers must fight for their lives as they attempt to call for backup before the rogue squad, led by the
backstabbing Sergeant Bartlett, can hunt them down to retrieve a case of missile guidance chips that Noah intercepted.
But Bartlett and his men do not count on Rana, whose ferocious
Gurkha training makes him a force to be reckoned with.
Rana Rae, played by Jean-Paul Ly.
Noah Brandt, played by Andrew-Lee Potts.
Bartlett, played by James Warren.
Espinosa, played by Adele Oni.
Trevors, played by Steven Blades.
Sage, played by Spencer Collings.
The Gentlemen is a 2019 action comedy film, directed and produced by Guy
Ritchie, co-written with Marn Davies and Ivan Atkinson.
Starring Matthew McConaughey, Charlie Hunnam, Henry Golding, Michelle Dockery, Jeremy Strong, Eddie Marsan, Colin Farrell, and Hugh Grant, the film
follows an American drug lord in England who is looking to sell his business, setting off a chain of blackmail and schemes to undermine him.
The Gentlemen premiered at the Curzon Mayfair Cinema on 3 December 2019, and was released in cinemas in the United Kingdom on
1 January 2020, by Entertainment Film Distributors, and in the United States on 24 January 2020, by STXfilms.
It received generally positive reviews from critics and was also a commercial
success, grossing $115 million worldwide against its $22 million budget.
A spin-off television series was released by Netflix in 2024
with Theo James starring in the lead role.
The tone is mind_bending.